KOBY HORNIBROOK

JavaScript Expert

CAREER OBJECTIVE

As a software developer who has over 5 years of experience, My works have been always remained the trusted and successful art stuff for from start-up business to wide range enterprise eCommerce. Mainly, I am focusing JS frameworks and libraries such as React, Three.js, D3.js and so on.

I would like to provide outstanding service with my creative ideas suited for modern architecture using my ability.

Hope to be an assistant and developer of your successful business.

CONTACT

- happysuperstar601@gmail.com
 - Sydney, Australia 💿
 - github.com/breadhead313

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng)
Computer Science
Monash University
2012 - 2016

SKILLS

- Three.js, D3.js, Chart.js, P5.js, Babylon.js, Knockout.js, VTK.js, Victory, Tween.js
- React, Angular, Vue
- Redux, Thunk, Saga, Rxjs, Ngrx, Vuex, Pinia
- Javascript, ECMAScript 6, Typescript
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, LESS, SASS, SCSS
- Material UI, Ant Design, Semantic UI, Chakra UI
- Next, Gatsby, Nuxt, Vuetify
- Unit Test: Mocha, Jest
- Agile, Scrum

WORK EXPERIENCE

Javascript Developer

Anakatech

March 2020 - December 2022

- Implemented lights, camera rig, preloader and animation with vanilla Javascript, Three.is and Tween.is.
- Presented an Intro to WebGL with Three.js at a front end web developer conference in 2021.
- Developed an intranet portal for the bank using React, TypeScript, GraphQL, and TailwindCSS
- Architected frontend application, GraphQL schema and queries -Designed prototype UX / UI with Sketch, Zeplin
- Conducted React training sessions for co-workers

UI/UX Developer

SoftServe

February 2019 - February 2020

- Created a compatible, custom client dashboard, reducing support tickets by 45%.
- Worked with UX/UI design teams improve existing applications and increase conversion rates by 20%.
- Designed multiple dynamic and browser compatible pages using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript(React, Redux).

Front End Developer

Mansion

May 2017 - January 2019

- Developed dynamic and interactive Real Estate website that ensured high traffic, page views and user experience.
- React.js, HTML and Bootstrap was used for Front-end and Back-end was Node.js. Constructed the logic of Rest APIs backend with node.js and tested backend server for bugs with Postman for QA team.
- Experience in working with Databases like MongoDB, MySQL and proficiency in writing SQL queries.